<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>puzzle on</title><link>https://cch0124.github.io/tags/puzzle/</link><description>Recent content in puzzle on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cch0124.github.io/tags/puzzle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>wireshark analysis Ann AppleTV</title><link>https://cch0124.github.io/blog/2020-08-02-ann-appletv/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cch0124.github.io/blog/2020-08-02-ann-appletv/</guid><description>題目 題目和內容，其中 Ann 的靜態 IP 是 192.168.1.10
What is the MAC address of Ann’s AppleTV? What User-Agent string did Ann’s AppleTV use in HTTP requests? What were Ann’s first four search terms on the AppleTV (all incremental searches count)? What was the title of the first movie Ann clicked on? What was the full URL to the movie trailer (defined by “preview-url”)? What was the title of the second movie Ann clicked on?</description></item><item><title>wireshark analysis Ann Skips Bail</title><link>https://cch0124.github.io/blog/2020-05-18-ann-skips-bail-wireshark/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cch0124.github.io/blog/2020-05-18-ann-skips-bail-wireshark/</guid><description>內容
題目 What is Ann’s email address? What is Ann’s email password? What is Ann’s secret lover’s email address? What two items did Ann tell her secret lover to bring? What is the NAME of the attachment Ann sent to her secret lover? What is the MD5sum of the attachment Ann sent to her secret lover? In what CITY and COUNTRY is their rendez-vous point? What is the MD5sum of the image embedded in the document?</description></item><item><title>wireshark analysis Ann’s Bad AIM</title><link>https://cch0124.github.io/blog/2020-05-17-ann-wireshark/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cch0124.github.io/blog/2020-05-17-ann-wireshark/</guid><description>題目網站
Ann’s computer, (192.168.1.158) sent IMs over the wireless network to this computer. 這一句話可發現 Ann 的 IP 為 192.168.1.158，和使用的應用程式。
該應用程式為IM 協定，tcp port 為 5190
題目 What is the name of Ann’s IM buddy? What was the first comment in the captured IM conversation? What is the name of the file Ann transferred? What is the magic number of the file you want to extract (first four bytes)? What was the MD5sum of the file?</description></item></channel></rss>